Bulkhead,
隔板
imagine you and I bumping into each other in the middle of
你我二人在这个鬼地方居然也会相遇
nowhere while tracking a stray energon signal.
都怪那个该死的能量信号
Yea, Breakdown,
没错 打击
it must be your lucky day.
今天是你的幸运日
Where is your pet human?
你的人类小宠物在哪儿？
How about when I finish with you, I'll pay her a visit?
等我消灭你之后 再去拜访她如何？
So the wrecker's got a soft spot.
戳到你的软肋了么？
As much as I'll miss our little reunions...
短暂的重逢让我终生难忘…
... hammer time.
这一锤送你上路！
Sir, we only have the resources to transport one.
长官 以我们现有的运力 只能带走一个
Take the victor.
带走那个打赢的
Marco. Marco.
“马可” “马可”
Marco!
“马可”！
Miko?
神子？
Hmmm... You're supposed to say "Polo"!
哼…你应该接着说“波罗”！
Eh?
呃？
Miko, let Ratchet know I need a Ground Bridge.
神子 跟救护车说 我需要环陆桥
Engaging the enemy on your own was foolish, Bulkhead.
单枪匹马独自迎敌 只是匹夫之勇 隔板
Breakdown jumped me.
打击偷袭我
I knew I could take 'em. Ugha!
我就知道他不行 啊！
Stay still.
别乱动
But we should see the other guy, right, Bulk?
看那家伙的惨状就知道了 对吧 小隔？
Uh, yea, about that...
呃 对了 关于这个…
You didn't torch him?
你没能消灭他？
Not exactly.
不完全是
I figured you all did.
我以为是你们干的
Oh...
哦…
When I came to, Breakdown was, just gone.
我醒来时 打击已经…不在了
I remember hearing a copter.
我记得有直升机的声音
Maybe it was Agent Fowler?
可能是福勒探员把他带走了？
Not me.
不是我
But I have an idea who.
但我猜到是谁了
Show me where this Con-napping occurred.
告诉我“绑虎事件”发生的位置
Lord Megatron,
威震天陛下
I fear Breakdown has gone missing.
打击现在下落不明
The Autobots?
是汽车人干的吗？
According to surveillance provided by the astonishingly accurate Soundwave,
根据那个精准无比的声波 提供的监视资料
Breakdown was abducted by humans.
绑架打击的是人类
You point?
你想说什么？
My strongest recommendation,
我强烈建议
we assemble a rescue team to hunt the vermin responsible for this outrage.
组建一支救援队 把那群自讨苦吃的害虫消灭干净！
Breakdown is on his own.
让打击自生自灭吧
Hah? Eh...
啊？呃…
Master?
主人的意思是？
If Breakdown allowed himself to be captured by those smaller than him,
如果打击轻易落在比他弱小的人类手中
he deserves whatever fate awaits him.
那只能说他气数已尽了
But Breakdown is a key player in our, eh...
但少了打击这个核心成员 我们…
Your wisdom reigns supreme, Lord Megatron...
您的智慧毋庸置疑 威震天陛下…
... for now.
…暂时的
What?
什么？
Filthy fleshlings,
肮脏的肉球！
who do you think you are?
你以为你们是谁？
We are MECH,
我们是机械党
and I, am Silas.
而我 就是塞拉斯
Release me now and I will let you live.
立即放了我 我可以留你们一条生路
I'm afraid you are far too valuable to us.
抱歉 对我们而言 你可是无价之宝
Hehe, Megatron will never pay a ransom.
呵呵 威震天从来不付赎金
Oh, you misunderstand.
哦 你误会了
We don't want a ransom.
我们要的不是赎金
We want only you.
而是你
All of you.
你的整个身体
This is where we picked up Bulkhead.
这就是我们发现隔板的地方
The Kamchatka Peninsula in Eastern Russia.
位于俄罗斯东部的堪察加半岛
Much of it was abandoned twenty years ago when its volcano first erupted.
二十年前首次火山喷发后 大部分地区被遗弃
My intel reported MECH activity there earlier today.
我有情报 今天早些时候 那里曾有机械党出没
MECH? You mean those techy guys?
机械党？你是指那群技术狂人？
The very ones who know of our existence on your planet.
那些人知道我们就在这个星球上
They must have tracked one of us there.
他们一定跟踪了我们
But what would they want with Breakdown?
但他们带走打击 目的何在？
What's it matter? They can have him.
这有什么？让他们放心走吧
Heh, yea. Dragged off by humans, Ha!
呵 是啊 被人类拖走了 哈！
Guess I softened him up for 'em, huh?
我也算是为人类做了善事 对吧？
Nya...
不害臊…
Ratchet, reactivate the previous Ground Bridge coordinates.
救护车 重新激活环陆桥的上一个坐标
We will rescue Breakdown.
我们要营救打击
What?
什么？
Optimus, you can't be serious.
擎天柱 你在开玩笑吧？
MECH can melt him down for all I care.
机械党把他拆了才好呢
Let the Cons rescue their own.
让虎子们自己去救人吧
It is unlikely that Megatron would bother with an errand of mercy.
威震天从来不会在乎一个手下的性命
OK. But this is Breakdown we are talking about.
好吧 可我们干嘛要去救打击
Sometimes we must rise above ourselves for the greater good.
有时候 为了顾全大局 我们必须看远一点
Oh, what's that supposed to mean?
噢 这话什么意思？
Breakdown's gotta be grateful and go all soft and join the cause?
打击会心怀感激 幡然悔悟 然后弃暗投明？
While it is unlikely that any Decepticon will choose the path of good,
尽管霸天虎改邪归正的可能性不大
even they possess the potential for change.
但他们毕竟有改变命运的潜力
Neh! I knew where this was headed.
切！我就知道你又要说教了
By greater good,
我说的顾全大局
I meant human kind.
是指人类
MECH presents a clear and present danger.
机械党是目前最明确的威胁
Prime's right.
擎天柱说的对
Two time.
大个子
We know MECH is obssessed with obtaining ground-breaking technology.
机械党正四处搜取最具突破性的科技
Which means we cannot allow Cybertronian biology
所以我们不能让塞博特恩生物科技
to fall into their hands.
落入他们的手中
Full disclosure,
开门见山
we intend to pull you apart.
我们打算把你肢解
Break you down,
给你一个“打击”
if you will.
怎么说都行
And we will utilize whatever we discover to develop a new generation of weaponary.
我们会利用所发现的一切 研发新一代武器
I'm afraid that you won't survive the process.
恐怕你不会活到解体完成
So thank you in advance for your sacrifice.
所以我要提前感谢你的无私奉献
MECH is very much in your debt.
机械党会牢记这份人情的
You're making a very big mistake, little man.
你正在犯一个天大的错误 小不点儿
When I'm finished with you, they'll have to scrape you off the floor!
我要把你干掉 让他们从地板上拼凑你的尸体！
Since you evidently aren't squeamish,
你显然不会晕血
I'll allow you to watch.
所以我让你观赏全程
Are his pain receptors disabled?
他的痛觉感受器都关闭了吗？
Good, then he won't make as much noise.
很好 这样他就不会大呼小叫了
Open him up.
拆开他
Come on, Bulk,
别这样 小隔
you got to go with.
你应该一起去
Don't wanna.
我就是不去
Bulkhead.
隔板
Optimus, I'm sorry.
大哥 抱歉
I just can't do it.
这种事我做不了
I support your choice.
我支持你的选择
- Wh-wh-what? - What?
- 什…什么？ - 什么？
Given your history with Breakdown,
考虑到你和打击之间的恩怨
your judgement maybe clouded,
你的判断力可能会受到影响
and thus jeopardize the mission.
这对任务有弊无利
Besides,
另外
the Decepticon maybe more in need of a medic than another warrior.
那名霸天虎更需要的是医生 而不是战士
Locked and loaded, Optimus.
我准备好了 擎天柱
Autobots, roll out!
汽车人 出发！
Fine, happy hunting.
好吧 祝你们马到成功
Uh!
呃！
Uh, what do you see?
呃 你想干点啥？
Creature double feature?
怪兽电影两集连放？
Sure.
随便你
Whooa, I'm in.
哇哦 算我一个
No signs of life.
没有生命迹象
Human or Cybertronian.
人类和塞博特恩人的都没有
Forget the tracks, Bumblebee.
别管那些胎痕了 大黄蜂
I'm picking up a faint energon signal three kliks north by northwest.
我收到一个微弱的能量信号 西北偏北方向 约四分钟路程
Breakdown.
是打击
But we shouldn't be getting a reading, unless...
但我们应该收不到他的信号 除非…
His energon's been spilled.
他的能量泄漏了
Dinolizard vs. Five-Headed Ape,
“哥斯拉大战五头猿”
you are missing the smack down.
你要错过大场面了
No, you are missing the smack down,
不 错过大场面的是你
which stinks,
气死我了
'cause Breakdown is your arch-enemy,
打击是你的老对手
not Optimus's,
不是擎天柱的
and definitely not MECH's.
更不是机械党的
Hugh... Miko, you don't understand.
唉…神子 你不懂
Breakdown and me,
打击和我
we go way back.
我们有很深的过节
You have no idea the things he's done.
你不知道 他干过什么坏事
I am not rescuing him OK?
我绝不会去救他 明白吗？
Not now, not ever!
这次不会 以后也没门儿！
Dah, you don't need to bromance him, Bulk.
我没让你去英雄救美男 小隔
You just need to beat him!
你需要的是打败他！
Uh, what?
呃 什么？
No rescue, no rematch.
不救他 你就没机会揍他了
This way.
走这边
Readings coming from right...
信号就来自…
... here.
…这里
Breakdown's eye.
打击的眼睛
MECH.
是机械党
What are you doing?
你要干嘛？
The optic receptors might have retained the final image received.
视觉接收器可能保存了最后收到的影像
What do you know?
你猜怎么着？
Weird science wins again.
科学怪人又赢了
Oh...
哦…
Well, well, Optimus Prime.
哎呀呀 擎天柱
A pleasure to "set eyes" on you again.
很高兴又“亲眼”见到你了
He's converted the optics to a two-way feed.
他把视学接收器改为双向传输了
And you must be Silas.
你一定就是塞拉斯
In the flesh.
正是本人
But being that our captive is not one of yours.
但由于我的俘虏不是你的人
I have to admit,
我得承认
I was expecting...
我以为来的会是…
... Megatron.
…威震天
In this circumstance,
在当前状况下
Autobots and Decpticons share a common foe.
汽车人和霸天虎有了共同的敌人
MECH is anything but common.
机械党跟你们那些敌人没有共同点！
Our guest is yielding quite a bit of information about your bio-mechanics,
我们的客人提供了大量 关于机械生命体的信息
as you can see.
正如你们所见
Although Breakdown himself can't see so well any more.
可惜打击自己看不大清楚了
We don't fear you!
我们不怕你！
Oh, but you should.
噢 你们早晚会怕的
In fact, I would strongly urge that you not stand your ground.
实际上 我强烈建议 你们别站得太死板了
It's a trap!
这是个陷阱！
Would this be a "roll out" kind of trap?
既然这样 你是不是该喊“出发”了？
Evacuate now!
火速撤离！
So, any idea where they're keeping the rest of Breakdown?
好了 谁知道他们把打击的零件藏在哪儿了？
Enjoying the view?
手术过程好看吗？
Ironically your would-be rescuers may be in more pieces than you right now.
真是讽刺 你的救星现在可能死无全尸了
Decpticons don't break that easy!
霸天虎没那么不堪一击！
Who said they were Decpticons?
我可没说他们是霸天虎
That doesn't make sense,
那不可能
Autobots wouldn't come to rescue me.
汽车人怎么会来救我
Marco!
“马可”！
You're supposed to say "Polo"!
你应该接着说“波罗”！
More grist for the mill.
又来了个送死的
It must be your lucky day.
今天是你的幸运日
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Getting you outta here.
救你出去
Yea, I don't believe it either.
没错 我也觉得太离谱
Can you walk?
你还能走么？
Uh, I think so.
呃 应该能
Can you run?
能跑么？
Never run when you can fight!
要死战到底 决不逃跑！
Just keep that thing pointed away from me, alright?
别用那玩意儿对着我 好么？
Creature double feature coming at you!
怪兽二人组杀过来喽！
You have some sort of escape plan?
你有逃跑的计划吗？
Yea, but you're not gonna like it.
有 但不合你的口味
Bulkhead to Optimus,
隔板呼叫擎天柱
Rendezvous to my coordinates,
到我的坐标处集合
I'm in need of backup.
我需要支援
Sir, incoming bogies.
长官 不明敌机正在接近
All units,
所有单位注意
disengage and initiate Omega Protocols.
撤出战斗 执行欧米加方案
Your backup?
是你的援兵吗？
Commander Starscream.
红蜘蛛指挥官！
Counsulting with the enemy, Breakdown?
居然和敌人私通？打击啊
But Bulkhead got me out of there.
是隔板救我出来的
Many spark felt thanks, Autobot.
我的火种充满感激之情 汽车人
Now destory him.
现在消灭他
But you...
但是…
Do you plan on joining their ranks anytime soon?
你打算过几天加入他们的队伍吗？
No? Then be done with them already!
不想吧？那就跟他们划清界限！
Tough break, Bulkhead,
很不幸 隔板
maybe the next life.
此恩来生再报
Destory him! Ah!
消灭他！啊！
Hammer time!
这一锤送你们上路！
Come on, I'll scrap all of you!
来啊 我把你们全都砸成碎片！
Engaging the enemy on your own was even more foolish this time, Bulkhead.
你单枪匹马独自迎敌 比上次还要鲁莽 隔板
But,
但是
I am honored that you saw fit to rescue your rival.
我很欣慰 你能顾全大局 营救自己的对头
You have truely risen above yourself.
你真的比以前成长了许多
Did you see,
你们看到了吗
I beat Breakdown and bashed them all with his own hammer!
我赢了打击 还用他的铁锤狠狠揍了他们一顿！
I won the rematch!
这次复赛我赢了！
I'm sure Miko would be proud.
神子一定会为你感到骄傲的
One day, you will repay you debt to me, Breakdown,
总有一天 你要还我一个人情 打击
the day it comes time to choose sides.
到时候 你可要选对立场！
Uh, between Bots and Cons?
呃 在轮子和虎子之间吗？
Between myself and Megatron.
在我本人和威震天之间
Incidentally,
顺便说一句
I suggest that Megatron never know of this rescue.
我建议你不要向威震天提起这次拯救行动
You do what him to think you overcame the puny humans on your own,
你也想让他觉得 是你自己打败那些小不点儿的
don't you?
没错吧？
The test subject escaped,
试验品逃走了
but we managed to sanitize the location and transfer
但我们及时清理了现场
most of the newly acquired data to another facility.
并将刚刚得到的数据 转移到了另一处基地
Our diagnostic scans of the subject's vital components
对试验品各关键部件的详细扫描
were thorough enough for us to initiate Project Chimera.
（Chimera 奇美拉  希腊神话中狮头、羊身、蛇尾的吐火怪物)
The power of the living mechines will,
这些活体机器的力量
some day soon,
不日之后
belong to MECH.
将属于机械党！